- [MAN] Help me. Help me!
- [gasps]
[♪ tense music playing]
Someone! Help me, please!
[gasps, grunts]
Ah!
[yelling]
They're going to kill me!
- Who are you?
- [gasps]
Please, you have to help me.
- Huh?
- [Raanas croaking]
- [yells]
- [Elymas gasps]
[croaking]
[screams]
- [croaking]
- [man shudders]
[whimpering]
- Stand back.
- Huh?
Ah! [whimpers]
Can you really take them down?
[gasps] Even though
you don't look the part,
are you actually
a famous adventurer?
[ELYMAS] No.
Huh?!
In fact, I just leveled up
for the first time
- in my whole life.
- [man gasps]
So you're hopeless?!
Stop! Come back!
You're too weak!
I'm much stronger than you,
and I can't handle
that many monsters!
Now take off that heavy armor!
We have to run!
[ELYMAS] Rampart Reflection
isn't perfect.
My defense needs to be greater
than my opponent's attack
to negate all damage.
If my defense is lower,
then it won't even activate.
Run away!
[croaking]
- [croaks]
- [squeals]
[croaking]
[ELYMAS] It's useless against
superior and unknown foes.
- [croaking]
- But still...
Let's go. Rampart Reflection!
- [grunts]
- [croaking]
Huh?!
[ELYMAS] I'm already familiar
with these starter enemies.
And I've boosted my defense
with skill tree bonuses
and equipment.
[croaking]
I can beat dozens of them.
No problem!
[grunts]
[gasps in disbelief]
[♪ heroic music playing]
- [Elymas sighs]
- [splutters]
[MAN] You brought down
that many?
Wait, who are you?
The name's Elymas Ed--
You're getting exactly
what you deserve.
Don't show your face here again!
If you ever use
the Edvaughn family name
outside of these walls,
I'll have your head
for such insolence!
I'm so sorry.
[huffs frustratedly]
[gasps] Hmm?
- [ELYMAS] No.
- [gasps]
The Heavy Knight,
Elymas.
[♪ opening theme song playing]
[Elymas sighs]
Huh?
[AUTOMATED VOICE] Level Eight
has been reached.
"Unwavering One" title acquired.
[ELYMAS] Display stats.
[ELYMAS] Hmm.
It seems pretty safe to assume
this world's systems work
just like Magic World's do.
Elymas.
I never introduced myself.
I'm Arus, and I left my village
to be an adventurer, but...
Hey, wait.
Uh, I was told
I would never be trusted
unless I was able to go out
and reach Level Three on my own.
I was panicking since
I couldn't get into a party.
But you really saved my neck.
I hope that you will allow me
to thank you.
[Elymas chuckles softly]
- Don't worry about it.
- Huh?
[ELYMAS] That was perfect
for grinding levels.
I will be taking all of
the Magic Stones, though.
Uh, yeah, of course.
So when we get back into town,
do you want
to form a party with me?
'Cause I have
a pretty strong lead, you know?
You must be struggling
to find work
by yourself as well.
Your class isn't too popular.
My son?! No!
It can't be!
- Look, such low stats!
- [gasps]
And they can't fight!
Heavy Knights
are totally worthless!
Everybody knows it's nothing
but a pitiful
and defective class!
[gasps]
But that simply isn't true!
They have the highest HP
and Defense, Father.
That's irrelevant,
just as you are!
- [thuds]
- [groans]
[ARUS] But I think
you're absolutely incredible.
And I have no doubt we would be
just perfect together.
I promise, I'll change
the other people's minds.
[Elymas sighs]
Nah, I'm okay.
[ARUS] What?
But why?
You were using a shield class
fighting style, right?
If you go it alone,
you won't ever be able
to level up.
So, don't be stubborn.
Huh?
[♪ somber music playing]
Sorry.
[sighs heavily]
[ELYMAS] Actually,
he's right about that.
When they're drawing
enemy attacks
and protecting allies,
defensive classes are normally
much more effective
during battle.
But if I just start
dragging along
a bunch of allies,
I'll have to start sharing EXP,
which really sucks
for the way I want to level up.
I'd like to gain different
items, skills, and titles too.
There's a good chance
people won't believe
what I tell them anyway.
[sighs determinately]
But more than that...
I don't have any time
to waste out here.
[Malice laughing]
There are still so many things
left for me to accomplish
if I want to become
a powerful Heavy Knight.
[grunts]
[birds chirping]
[ARUS] Come on, Elymas.
I'm saying this
to try and help you.
Though you're truly amazing,
you're only going to get so far
using your current method.
There's no point
in farming Raana forever,
is there?
Let's aim higher together.
[ELYMAS] Uh.
[gasps] Huh?
[ARUS] Huh?
Huh? Hmm.
[leaves rustling]
[♪ eerie music playing]
Huh? [gasps]
Huh? Huh?
Hmm?
[gasps] Huh?
[creature chittering]
[Arus screams]
[rumbling]
- [screeches]
- [Arus shrieks in terror]
Huh. No way!
What is that doing out here?!
- [screeches]
- [Arus gasps]
[Arus shrieks in terror]
[grunts] Display stats!
[growling]
[ELYMAS] An Ariandype.
Looks like it's double
my current level.
[screeches]
- [whimpers]
- It had been using
its Creepy-Crawly skill to hide.
That thing can also use
slowing poison too.
And its Flaming Claw skill
is also deadly.
Rampart Reflection
is practically useless
against higher-level enemies.
Without a defense that's equal
to double their attack,
it won't be activated.
[whimpering]
If I eat a Flaming Claw,
it'll one-shot me.
I lured it here.
Damn it, it's my fault.
[breathing shakily]
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
I'll keep it busy
so you can escape.
So don't you worry
about a thing.
I'll just, uh...
No, it's all right.
[whimpers] Huh?
- I got this. So just stay back.
- Huh?
Hey, wait!
Stop!
- Are you out of your mind?
- No.
Huh?
[growling]
[ELYMAS] This battle...
isn't unwinnable.
[ARUS] It'd be impossible
for a newbie like you
to take down an Ariandype!
Listen, I know
I said that you're incredible,
and you are.
But you can't do this!
- [growls]
- [ELYMAS] Display stats.
Huh?
[ELYMAS] I've still got
the seven skill points
I gained earlier.
If I want to stand a chance,
I'd better put them all into
Oath of the Heavy Armor!
[AUTOMATED VOICE] The Disarm
skill has now been acquired.
[ELYMAS] The moment I strike
and land a solid hit,
Disarm will temporarily lower
my opponent's attack power.
It drops by 20%
for a one-minute duration,
to be exact.
That's the skill I'll need
to beat the Ariandype.
[grunts]
All right then. Let's go!
- Time for me to take you on!
- [screeches]
Really?
[sighs]
[ELYMAS] The moment I strike
and land a solid hit,
Disarm will temporarily lower
my opponent's attack power.
It drops by 20%
for a one-minute duration,
to be exact.
[sighs]
[grunts] All right then.
Let's go!
- [growls]
- Time for me to take you on!
[growls]
It's high-risk, high reward!
[grunts]
But there's nothing
that fires me up more!
[whooshing]
[ARUS] Huh?
- [screeches]
- [Elymas grunts]
[grunts]
Bring it on, Ariandype!
- [screeches]
- [grunts]
I know its reach
and attack patterns.
I won't get hit that easily.
[roars]
[grunting]
[gasps] What is that?!
[Elymas grunts]
I'll eat this attack...
- [squelching]
- ...on purpose!
Elymas!
[ELYMAS] And then I'll use...
[grunts]
[yells] Disarm!
[growls]
[ELYMAS]
That barely made a dent.
But now
it ought to be debuffed.
[roars]
What? Oh, shit!
[growling]
Look out!
[grunts]
Huh?
[Ariandype growling]
[gasps] Huh?
Elymas.
I'm afraid
that's not gonna work.
Poison Beam costs seven MP.
[sighs, grunts]
And Flaming Claw costs five MP.
[roars]
- [grunts]
- [slashes]
- [yells] Disarm!
- [screeches]
[ELYMAS] That's a second Disarm
and a 40% attack reduction.
When I'm holding position,
the title I earned
after leveling up,
Unwavering One,
buffs my defense by 10%.
Okay. I'm ready to do this.
The differences in our ability
can be overcome using knowledge.
[panting]
Victory is mine!
[Ariandype growling]
- [grunts, yells]
- [sword clangs]
Huh? What the...
[Elymas panting]
[growling]
[grunts]
[growls]
[roars]
[shrieks]
Rampart Reflection!
[whimpers, gasps]
[sighs]
[breathing weakly]
It's all over now.
- [grunts]
- [Ariandype groans]
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Level 12 has been reached.
Four skill points acquired.
[pants, gasps]
Additional points
cannot be added
to Oath of the Heavy Armor
at this time.
[ELYMAS]
I've seen this message before.
[groans]
So that Magic World feature
made it out here, too, huh?
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Oath of the Heavy Armor
has reached Level 15.
Parry skill has been acquired.
[ELYMAS] Either way,
now I've got my basic skills.
Uh, seriously,
who in the world are you?
Well, after everything
I've just seen here,
you probably just could
go it alone.
I don't know why I was worried.
It's clear you can take care
of yourself.
[ELYMAS] Sorry, I guess--
[groaning, coughs]
[ARUS] Hey, wait a minute!
You were just poisoned!
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Status effect. Poisoned.
- [ARUS] I'll escort you to town.
- [ELYMAS] Thank you, Arus.
[groans weakly]
[ARUS] As far as I'm concerned,
it's the least I can do.
[ELYMAS] Sorry.
[groaning weakly]
[ARUS]
You saved my life back there.
Hope we meet each other
again one day. [chuckles]
[♪ gentle music playing]
[sighs]
[Elymas groaning]
[gasps]
But that simply isn't true!
They have the highest HP
and Defense, Father.
That's irrelevant,
just as you are!
- [thuds]
- [groans]
Rampart Reflection!
[gasps sharply]
I always thought
Elymas couldn't bear the burden
of being your true heir.
[seething]
[ELYMAS] The day after I
beat the Ariandype,
I made my way down to
the Rondalm Adventurer's Guild
to register as an adventurer.
[indistinct chatter]
[ELYMAS] I'd like to register
as an adventurer.
[indistinct chatter]
[MAN 1] Hmm.
- [MAN 2] Hmm?
- [MAN 3] Huh?
Name's Elymas. I'm Level 12.
My class is Heavy Knight.
I can't believe he'd admit that.
[laughs] Why even bother?
- How embarrassing!
- [all laugh]
[MAN 3]
Heavy Knights are useless!
Oh, I see. So, you're
a defensive class, then.
Yes, sir. Understood.
[AUTOMATED VOICE] F-rank
adventurer Elymas, approved.
[ELYMAS] It's official.
As of right now,
I'm a proper adventurer.
There are seven adventurer ranks
in total.
To enter a dungeon,
it's required that each member
of a party
has at least an E-ranking.
And my ranking determines
the number of skill points
I can add
to Oath of the Heavy Armor.
So, I need to hurry and move up
to E as soon as possible.
Oh, right.
- Hey, look there.
- [gasps]
Do you think that low-level
Heavy Knight's
looking for a party to join?
Who'd let trash like that
be part of their group? [laughs]
[MAN 2] Do any of you
need my help?
There aren't many parties
actively looking
for shield users,
so this may take more time
than you expected.
- [ELYMAS] I see.
- I-I'm sorry about this.
Well, I can always worry about
finding a party later.
But for now...
Huh?
[ELYMAS] I'm glad I was able
to take this Magic Bag.
Seems like it can store
countless items.
I'd like to trade
my Magic Stones.
- [all gasp]
- [MAN 4] What did he say?
[MAN 5] Just look at them.
[gasps] You gathered these
all by yourself?
- [ELYMAS] Yeah. It was just me.
- [gasps]
And be sure to put that down
in your report.
- [all gasp]
- [WOMAN] Huh? Um, okay.
He isn't lying, is he?
What's up
with that Heavy Knight?
Obviously,
the guy's been cheating.
[scoffs]
[ELYMAS] I finished registering,
and I've got enough funds
to cover my living expenses.
What's coming next is enough
to really get my Magic World
player blood pumping!
So would you happen to know
of any promotion quests
that I could take?
Huh?
- Um.
- Hmm?
Well, uh,
yes, I do, technically.
Huh?
- [both breathing anxiously]
- [gulps]
[all breathing nervously]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[both chuckle]
[growls]
[MAN] There's been a lot of talk
about this Raid Quest.
Apparently, a clown has chosen
to join us tonight.
Must be you, Elymas.
There are plenty
of novices like you
who completely underestimate
guilds and monsters.
- [all gasp]
- You managed to beat
an Ariandype at Level 12?
That means nothing to me!
Adventuring isn't so easy!
I'll teach you a lesson!
One you aren't ever
going to forget!
[growls]
[growling]
[ELYMAS] Well, this sucks.
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[ELYMAS]
I wanted to join a Raid Quest
so I can raise
my adventurer rank
and get past
the current advancement cap
on my skill tree.
But I've had a bad feeling
about this group
since I arrived here.
Some are seasoned and arrogant,
others are new and afraid.
I just hope
nothing happens to us.
Next time, "The Raid Quest."
If we can just back
each other up,
we won't have anything to fear.